https://heartlandharps.com/about/heartland-harps-and-music-inc-privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policyadmin2019-09-18T15:29:15-04:00
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy was last modified on 05/23/18.
Our company, Heartland Harps and Music Inc., operates http://wwww.heartlandharps.dev (the “Site”). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.
We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.
Information Collection and Use
While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that we can use to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but it is not limited to your name, telephone number, email address, street address (“Personal Information”).
Log Data
Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, pages of our Site that you visit, time and date of your visit, time spent on those pages and other applicable statistics.
Your privacy is very important to us here at our Heartland Harps and Music Inc. Any collected Personal Information will be for internal use only. This policy statement is in compliance with Canadian Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA), European Union General Data Protection Regulation Act (GDPR), and Australian Privacy Protection Act (AU Privacy Act). This policy also meets the criteria for EU Cookies Directive regulation in line with any of our online activity tracking capabilities.
